Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera MC.334
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera
1835-2024, ongoing
1920-2005
New York University Archives
MC.334
214.77 Linear Feet in 394 manuscript boxes, 9 half manuscript boxes, 33 oversize flat boxes, 2 custom boxes, and 5 folders in shared housing
274 websites in 274 archived websites.
The New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera is an artificial collection containing NYU publications and promotional material dating from 1835 to 2022, documenting multiple NYU schools, clubs, organizations, and divisions. The publications typically contain newsletters, bulletins, websites, and magazines. The promotional print material in this collection includes publicity brochures, booklets and posters.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Arrangement
The series are listed in numerical order by their University Archives Record Group number and title (e.g., RG 1.0. All-University). Within each series, the material is listed, beginning with publications arranged alphabetically by title, then followed by promotional material and ephemera listed in chronological order.
Historical Note
This collection was created by University Archives staff to provide access to unrestricted NYU publications and promotional material.
Custodial History
This collection was created by NYU University Archives staff. Accretions have been received in 2019, 2021, 2023, and 2023 and have been documented by the following accessions: 20919.119, 2021.021, 2022.030, 2022.031, 2022.078, 2022.079, 2023.029, and 2023.046. Weekly bulletins of the Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences from accession 2023.046 were treated as an administrative transfer to the New York University Archives from the Courant Institute in the summer of 2023 when the Courant Institute Library closed. An issue of the journal MYCRO was transferred by Katya Greenberg in January 2024 as accession 2024.008.
Websites were selected by NYU University Archives staff through the use of Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. Websites were not accessioned prior to October 2018. Websites added to the web archives after October 2018 are associated with the following accession numbers: 2019.106, 2019.107, 2019.122, 2020.012, 2020.013, 2020.041, 2021.003, 2021.036, 2021.037, 2021.038, 2021.039, 2021.040, 2022.029, 2022.033, 2022.070, 2022.072, 2022.078, 2022.079, 2023.014, 2023.023, 2023.030, 2023.057, 2024.007, 2024.018, 2024.047, and 2024.055.
Materials found in series RG 39.12 Glee Club were transferred from the New York University Archives Photograph Collection (PHOTO 00001) in May 2024. The accession number associated with this accretion is 2024.034.
Scope and Contents
This is an artificial collection of printed material and publications from over 500 different schools, divisions, and organizations within New York University dating from 1835 to 2022. The publications typically include newsletters, event calendars, bulletins, websites, and magazines. The promotional material and ephemera contains brochures, booklets, mailers, and pamphlets, as well as posters. Material in the collection was separated from their original NYU University Archives record groups and placed together for easier access. This is not necessarily a complete set of any of these publications and it is possible that the same titles and print material are also found within their original record groups.
Some materials in this collection contain racist, abilist, and sexist imagery and text. Both RG 21.32 and RG 39.30's titles were retained due to their historical context. Both RG 39.30's group name and publication title were created by an NYU Black student group.
Separated Materials
Items removed from the collection include: Proofs: The Dental Trade Journal; N.Y.U. Graduate School Abridgements of Thesis (1948-1949 and 1949-1950); and Universities and Their Sons (Vol 2, 1899)
Material belonging in other collections / record groups were removed and accessioned into their appropriate collections.
Appraisal
Between March and July 2022, eight cartons of duplicate material were removed and shredded as decided by the University Archivist.
The following books had available copies existing in Bobst Library and were removed from the collection: Bound Proceedings of the NYU Institute on Federal Taxation (editions: 1945-1948, 1954); Bound Proceedings for the Conference on Charitable Foundations (editions: 1955, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1963, 1965)
For the archived websites, robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored with the permission of the content owner.
Accruals
Majority of websites are accrued annually, with some captured semiannually and quarterly.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
Publicity.; Serial publications.; Posters.; Student activities.; College student newspapers and periodicals.; College students -- New York (N.Y.); Magazines (Periodicals); Glee clubs; New York University
- RG 1.0. All-University, 1836-2020
  - 365, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - All-Square Student Calendar, 1966-1971 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - All-University Calendar, 1913-1918, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 1-6, Box 3, Folder 1-5)
  - All-University Calendar, 1928, 1934-1940 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - All-University Calendar, 1946-1950 (Box 5, Folder 1-3, Box 6)
  - All-University Calendar, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 1-4, Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - All-University Calendar, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
  - All-University Calendar, 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 1-3)
  - All-University Calendar, 1981-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1-11)
  - Community Calendar, 1966-1973, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3-11)
  - Internal, 1965-1974 (Box 32, Folder 1-7, Box 33, Folder 1-6, Box 34, Folder 1-3)
  - International Events Calendar, 1992, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - New York, 1926-1930 (Box 11, Folder 2-5, Box 12, Folder 1-3, Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - New-York Quarterly Magazine, 1836-1837 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - New York University Bulletin, 1911, 1939, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 3-5)
  - New York University Bulletin, 1949-1969 (Box 15, Folder 1-8, Box 16, Folder 1-4)
  - New York University Daily News, 1922-1923 (Box 46, Folder 1-10)
  - New York University Magazine, March-April 1847 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - New York University Report, 1974-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1-6, Box 18, Folder 1-8, Box 128, Item 1)
  - New York University Weekly Calendar, 1960-1966 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - New Yorker, 1909-1910, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 4, Box 45, Folder 14)
  - NYU Event Hotline, 1985-1991 (Box 19, Folder 5, Box 49, Folder 1-5, Box 50, Folder 1-4)
  - NYU Events, 1992-1995 (Box 47, Folder 3-5)
  - NYU Hotline, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - NYU Minute, 2005-2017 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - NYU Notebook, 1958-1965 (Box 19, Folder 9, Box 20, Folder 1-7)
  - The NYU Scene, 1981-1986, undated (Box 20, Folder 8-12)
  - The NYU Today Hotline, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - On the Square, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Tempo, 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Triangle, 1897-1904 (Box 21, Folder 3-6, Box 22, Folder 1-4, Box 23, Box 24, Folder 1-3)
  - The Triangle, 1904-1906 (Box 25, Folder 1-2, Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - The University, 1886-1890 (Box 26, Folder 4-5, Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - The University Forum, 1890-1894 (Box 27, Folder 3-7, Box 28, Folder 1-3, Box 29, Box 30)
  - University Heights Center Weekly Calendar of Events, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The University Item, 1894-1897, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 1-5, Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - View, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures and Souvenir Booklet, 1892-1894 (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Book -- Universities and Their Sons: New York University..., 1901 (Box 41, Box 42)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Book -- Universities and Their Sons: New York University..., 1903 (Box 43, Box 44)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Alumni Catalogue, 1906 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Song Book and Event Announcements, 1915-1916 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures, 1920-1923 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Book with Pictorial Review of the University, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures and Campus Map, 1924-1928 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Book with a Pictorial and Historical Review of the University, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 5-7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures, 1929-1959 (Box 35, Folder 8-9, Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- University Program Brochures, circa 1950-1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- The Story of NYU, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- The Torch that Lights a City, circa 1954 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Promotional Booklets, 1964-1969 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- A Graphic Presentation Concerning New York University..., 1965 (Box 36, Folder 9, Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- University Capital Program Brochures, May 1969 (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Student Recruitment Brochures, 1970-1977 (Box 37, Folder 5-6, Box 38, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Student Recruitment Posters with Postcards, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Booklets and Brochures, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Faculty Funding Opportunities Booklet, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Booklets and Brochures, 1980-1983 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- NYU 150 Year Anniversary Calendar Book, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Student Recruitment Brochures, 1982-1988 (Box 39, Folder 2-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures and Booklets, 1988-1999 (Box 39, Folder 7-11, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures and Booklets, 2000-2006 (Box 40, Folder 2-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Postcards and Stickers, 2016, 2020 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
- RG 2.0. Board of Trustees (Council), 2002
  - Promotional Materials and Ephemera, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- RG 3.2. Office of Compliance and Risk Management, and Office of Equal Opportunity, 2011-ongoing
  - Compliance Matters, 2011-2016 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Compliance Matters Newsletter, May 2014-ongoing
    Scope and Contents
    The Compliance Matters newsletter is a publication from the Office of Compliance and Risk Management. Its first issue was published in 2011. Compliance Matters provides updates about important ethics, compliance, risk management, equal employment opportunity, and disability issues. It also includes information about new and/or revised university policies and compliance regulations.
- RG 5.0. Office of the Provost, 2002
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Curricular Development Challenge Fund Brochure, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- RG 5.0.6. Office of the Provost -- Global Views, 2001-2007
  - Global Views, 2001-2007 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- RG 5.0.7. Distinguished Administrator Award, 2002, 2004
  - Promotional Poster, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2002, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- RG 5.0.8. Distinguished Teaching Award, 1991, 2002, 2009
  - Promotional Posters, 2000-2009 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1991, 2002, 2009 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- RG 5.1. Office of Global Programs, 2013-2019
  - Promotional Poster, circa 2013-2015 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Booklets, Brochures, Mailers, 2013-2019 (Box 52, Folder 5-9)
- RG 5.4. Diversity Programs, 2016
  - Promotional Brochures, 2016 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- RG 6.1.1. Torch Club, 2000-2003, 2010
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochures, Calendars, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Event Invitation, 2010 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- RG 6.2. Provost of University Heights, circa 1930s-1970s
  - Heights Graduate Newsletter, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- University Heights Campus Photograph Book, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 53, Folder 3)
- RG 6.4.2. Office of Community Service, 1995-2008
  - C-Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Service Matters, 1996-2008 (Box 53, Folder 6-11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Brochure, Announcements, 1997, 2000, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
- RG 6.6. Office of Sustainability/Office of the Assistant Vice President for Sustainability, 2022-ongoing
  - NYU Sustainablog, May 2017-ongoing
    The NYU Sustainablog highlights the initiatives and participants of NYU Office of Sustainability programs. Topics on the blog include climate change, compost, recycling, veganism and vegetarianism, urban agriculture, food waste, bicycling, water conservation, news about sustainable initiatives around NYU, and tips to be more sustainable. The website wasredesigned in 2019. The blog dates back to 2015.
  - Sustainability News, May 2022-ongoing
    Sustainability News is NYU's newsletters for students, faculty, administrators, and staff on sustainability initiatives, the progress of projects at the university, programs, events, deadlines, spotlights, and tips on going green.
- RG 7.0. Office of VP External Affairs, 1987-1998
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1998 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- RG 7.1. Office of the Senior VP University Development and Alumni Giving, 1919-2020
  - Bulletin -- NYU Endowment Fund, 1919-1920 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Plus, 1970-1974 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Report, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Update, 1980-1981, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Wrapup, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Current Financial Planner, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - First-Year Report -- NYU Billion Dollar Campaign, 1983, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Insights, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Interest, 1972, 1974, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Progress Report, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Report, 1976-1979 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 1918-1920 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Endowment Fund Report and Honor Roll of Subscribers, 1921-1924 (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Booklet, circa 1924-1925 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Bequest Foundation Committee Booklet, 1932 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Information Packet The Great Awakening, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Gift Report and Guides for Donors -- Brochures and Booklets, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Estate Planning, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Scholars Program, circa 1960 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- University Research and the City Booklet, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- The University and the Disadvantaged Booklet, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- The New York University Campaign, 1969-1978 (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- One Hundred Million Dollar Special Fund, 1982-1984 (Box 55, Folder 10-11, Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Billion Dollar Campaign, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Endowed Professorships, circa 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2000-2006, 2013 (Box 56, Folder 4-6)
- RG 7.1.1. Capital Program, 1964-1967
  - Capital News, 1964-1967 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 8-10, Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Funding Opportunity Presentation Booklets, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 3-7, Box 58, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Funding Opportunity Presentation Booklets, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 1-7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 8-10)
- RG 7.1.2. Office of Annual Giving, 1990-1994, 1997
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1990-1994, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 1-5)
- RG 7.2. Office of Senior Vice President, University Relations and Public Affairs, 1983-2018
  - New York University Government Relations Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - NYU Arts, 2015-2018 (Box 60, Folder 7-10)
  - NYU in the News Bulletin Board, 1983-1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - NYU Research, 2004-2011, 2017-2018 (Box 60, Folder 11, Box 61, Folder 1, Box 45, Folder 7-9)
  - NYU Research Digest, 2011-2016 (Box 61, Folder 2-7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 8-9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2007-2008 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- RG 7.2.3. Advertising and Publication Services / Publications Bureau, undated, November 2020-ongoing
  - NYU News, May 2010-ongoing
    NYU News, also known as NYU Today, contains press releases, research updates, event listings, and other articles related to news from the NYU community. The website features news related to arts and culture, business and entrepreneurship, campus and community, education and social sciences, engineering and technology, science, health and medicine, and law and policy. Featured articles date back to 2014. NYU News also published series on alumni, Black History Month, Pride Month, Women's History Month, sustainability, students spotlights, NYU Holodeck Project, staff and faculty, courses, and New York City.
  - Alumni Magazine, November 2020-ongoing
    The website contains issues of the NYU Alumni Magazine dating back to Fall 2007. lt is a general interest publication covering the university's array of alumni, faculty, and student newsmakers in politics, arts and culture, academia, entertainment, sports, business, science, medicine, technology and more.
  - NYU Arts Digest, September 2022-ongoing
    The NYU Arts Digest is a biannual web publication celebrating the creativity and impact of the arts and humanities throughout the university. Sections in the publication include Features, Campus Canvas, Gallery Tour, Highlights, and Poetry Pause. The publication was launched in Fall 2021.
  - Scope Magazine, August 2022-ongoing
    Scope is the annual research magazine of New York University. It includes sections titled Distillations, Question, Hypothesis, Experiment, Features, The Science Behind..., and Think Tank. The publication dates back to 2020.
  - Promotional Posters, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
- RG 7.2.4. Office of Government and Community Affairs, 1973-2008
  - Community Calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - New York University Community Newsletter, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - NYU Leadership Campaign, 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1980-1992 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2006-2008 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- RG 7.2.7. Office of Community Engagement, 1987-2018
  - NYU Community Fund, 2004-2016 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2009, 2017-2018 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
- RG 7.3.1. Office of Radio and TV, 1975-1994
  - Columbine, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- RG 7.3.1.1. Sunrise Semester, 1960-1976
  - Sunrise Semester Newsletter, 1960-1965 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1957-1958 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Emmy Awards-Related, 1957-1960 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Radio Highlights Clippings, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1976-1982, undated (Box 62, Folder 11-14)
- RG 7.3.3. Office of News Bureau / Information Services, 1930-1931, 1957
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1930-1931 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- RG 7.4. Commencement and Special Events / University Events, 1966
  - New York University Commencement Bulletin, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- RG 7.5. Office of Alumni Relations
  - NYU Alumni Connect, April 2014-May 2018
    NYU Alumni Connect is a monthly email newsletter including alumni and faculty profiles, featured NYU news, and a stories from the University Archives. Alumni Connect dates back to January 2010.
  - NYU Alumni Magazine, May 2014-November 2020
    NYU Alumni Magazine is a general interest publication covering the university's array of alumni, faculty, and student newsmakers in politics, arts & letters, academia, entertainment, sports, and more. It is produced by a team of freelance writers, editors, and designers, and distributed to nearly 250,000 alumni, faculty, and parents across the country. The magazine is available online back to Fall 2007.
  - NYU Class Notes, 2016-2017, 2024-ongoing (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Class Notes lists alumni accomplishments, milestones, and obituaries. The notes are organized by sector then by school.
  - NYU Alumni & Friends Connect, August 2022-ongoing
    NYU Alumni & Friends Connect is a monthly newsletter for New York University Alumni and others associated with New York University. The articles include student profiles, alumni profiles, alumni events, alumni benefits, awards, and other news from the university and New York City. The newsletter dates back to 2016.
  - NYU Alumni News, May 2023-ongoing
    NYU Alumni News features news from New York University alumni and friends. It features alumni awardees, spotlights on alumni network groups, NYU leadership updates, volunteer profiles, and other news.
  - Torchlight, April 2024
    The Torchlight newsletter contains information on chairitable giving arrangements for NYU alumni and other community members. The newsletter published from 2016-2021.
- RG 8.2. Human Resources / Personnel Services, 1965-2008
  - Benefits Newsletter, 1984-2001 (Box 255, Folder 1-4)
  - NYU Staff Newsletter, 1971-1974, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 5-9)
  - NYU Umbrella, 1984-1985 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Staff Newsletter, 1965-1969 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Supervisor's Network, 1985-2006 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - Training Network, 1983-1984 (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - Working at NYU, 2002-2007 (Box 195, Folder 8-9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Personnel Services, 1967-1972 (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Personnel Services, 1982-1999 (Box 64, Folder 1-7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Personnel Services, 1999-2008 (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
- RG 8.2.1. Office of Work-Life Services, 1998-2004